well what's up with my people first of
bueno qué pasa con mi gente antes que
all I want to tell everyone who
nada quiero decir a todo el mundo que
is coming to this video to
está llegando a este vídeo que os
subscribe jce not only to this channel
suscriba jce no solamente a este canal
but also to my main channel if
sino también a mi canal principal que si
I remember the time it takes to describe
me acuerdo los tardando la descripción
the topic that I'm going to cover now I've already
del tema que voy a tratar ahora ya lo he
covered it in one of my live shows and almost
tratado en uno de mis directos y casi
every night I'm live I don't have a
todas las noches en directos no tengo un
fixed schedule okay just to be there
horario fijo vale solo estar algunas
sometimes at 8 other times at 10 and other times at
veces a las 8 otras a las 10 y otras a
1 in the morning when I get some
la una la mañana cuando me sale medel
turrón let's say or when it comes to me
del turrón digamos o cuando me nace es
but almost every day and that are to be
pero casi todos los días y que son a ser
live on the platform you know
directos en la plataforma de you know
okay if you have subscribed and following me on
vale si te has suscrito y me siguiendo a
the networks then you won't miss any
las redes pues nos perderéis ningún
directories you will find out about the salsa singer before
directorios enteraréis del salsero antes
any part okay all the salsa singer
que cualquier parte vale todo el salsero
all the controversy and all the controversy
toda la polémica y toda la controversia
that happens on social networks will be
que se pasa en las redes sociales estará
on this my other channel and live if you
en este mi otro canal y en directo si
want to find out about everything follow me today I'm going to
queréis enterar de todo seguidme hoy voy
talk about well I've already talked about this
a hablar de bueno esto ya lo he hablado
I showed it in one of my live shows so I
lo enseñé en uno de mis directos así que
ask all of you who are in  the
os pido a todos que los que estáis en el
chat that you do the new is worth it as if you
chat que os hagáis lo nuevo vale como si
had never seen it you act
no hubieras visto nunca os hacéis los
new and that's it okay as you already know
nuevos y punto vale como ya sabéis en
these days it has gone very viral and there has been
estos días pues ha hecho muy viral y se
a lot of talk about
ha tratado mucho sobre
well the topic surrounding win digital but
bueno el tema que rodea win digital pero
what I want
lo que os quiero
what I want to show you is curious because it has
lo que quiero enseñar es curioso porque
gone very viral a click on wind
se ha hecho muy viral un clic sobre wind
and laughing at the forward without imagination
y riéndose de delantero sin imaginación
because she thought he had lost his
porque ella creía que había perdido el
job on Facebook it turns out that
trabajo de facebook resulta ser que se
that treatment has gone viral where she
ha hecho viral ese trato donde ella se
laughs at the forward and makes fun of him but I have
ríe de delantero y se burla pero yo he
been watching the right a little more
estado viendo el derecho un poquito más
extensively and there are other curious things
extensamente y hay otras cosas curiosas
that we should comment on okay and they have
que deberíamos comentar vale y han
gone totally unnoticed and
pasado totalmente desapercibida y la
people have overlooked it I don't know
gente lo ha pasado por alto no sé por
why they have only caught the clip of the
qué solamente han pillado el clip de
forward and have not given importance to
delantero y no le han dado importancia a
what is being said around it which for me
lo que se comenta alrededor que para mí
is much stronger or rather it turns out
es mucho más fuerte o sea resulta ser
that he from
que él
here more or less from minute
a partir de aquí más o menos del minuto
45 30 hours and that's when he talks about Dylan
45 30 horas y es cuando habla de dylan
but not all to speak ill of me and
pero no todos para hablar mal de mí y
defame me and blame me for things that I
difamarme y ponerme culpable cosas que
almost do not do full at
no hago casi yo full
least six minutes 45  and a half
al menos seis minutos 45 y medio
well
bueno
you your friends please blowtorch of
usted tus amigos por favor soplete de
good image is not going to make you speak
buena imagen no te va a poner a hablar
badly of another who is in the same company
mal de otro que está en la misma empresa
as you this famous clip
que tú este famoso clip
[Music]
[Música]
but it is that if we go back a few
pero es que si nos volvemos algunos
minutes before from 43 let's say no
minutos antes a partir del 43 digamos no
her in the context and this is why the
ella en el contexto y por esto sale el
name of the forward comes up in the conversation
nombre del delantero en la conversación
it is because she is talking about the
es porque ella está hablando de los
salt channels you are criticized for controversial
canales de sal se os critica polémica
calling them through the channels that we
llamarlos a través de los canales que
treat the weeks and that is why
tratamos los los semanas y por eso
someone mentions forward in the chat
alguien le menciona delantero en el chat
and her name comes up but the thing is
y sale su nombre pero es que la cosa es
that she in this conversation that lasts a few
que ella en esta charla que dura unos
minutes is talking about the salsa channels
minutos está hablando sobre los canales
because your carcinogenic morals said it
porque tu moral cancerígeno dijeron que
was a lie
era mentira
happens with the edition they are receiving so
pasa con la edición están recibiendo
many this
tantos
can this can bring problems
esto puede esto le puede traer problemas
with the copyright
con el copyright
because she is putting music is that she
porque está poniendo música es que ella
directly we put
lo directo ponemos
Edward Enrique from what I began to
edward enrique de lo que me puse a
tell her maximize her vision I never
decirle maximizar su visión jamás lo
said it well the opposite
dije bien lo contrario
okay this I have to say that it is
vale esto tengo que decir que es
totally true
totalmente cierto
she never called the blonde sexist I do not
ella nunca llamó machista el rubio yo no
that site in student in some of my old
ese sitio en alumno en algunas de mis
videos old we did I have
vídeos antiguos antiguo hicimos
come to say that she called
he llegado a decir que ella llamase
sexist  the blonde because when a
machista el rubio porque cuando una
truth is repeated so many times among so many
verdad se repite tanto entre tantos
channels in the end it becomes
canales al final como que se convierte
a rumor, a gossip that's half true, I don't
en un rumor en un chisme medio verdad no
know if in some video I would have
sé si en algún vídeo yo llegaba a
said it but I think not because I know
decirlo pero creo que no porque sé
perfectly well that what she said
perfectamente que lo que ella dijo ella
is true that she was throwing [ __ ] at
sí que es verdad que estaba tirando caca
the blonde with that video, the one from the curly site
al rubio con ese vídeo al del sitio rulo
discriminated when the blonde had
discriminaba cuando el rubio no tenía
no need or obligation
ninguna necesidad ni ninguna obligación
to why invite her to a tournament that he
de por qué invitarla a un torneo que él
does and invites whoever he feels like doing
hace e invita a quien le sale a él de
okay but she wasn't
sus partes vale pero ella no lo habíamos
sexist in fact what she said was the complete
machista de hecho lo que dijo fue todo
opposite I don't know why the blonde didn't
lo contrario no sé por qué el rubio no
invite me I don't think it's because he's
me invita no creo que sea porque sea
sexist because he's invited other
machista porque ha invitado a otras
women I don't think it's because I
mujeres no creo que sea porque yo
used low cut bottoms because he's invited other
utilicé escotes porque ha invitado otras
women who used low cut bottoms I don't think it's
mujeres que utilizar escote no creo que
she says the complete opposite and I don't know
sea ella dice todo lo contrario y no sé
how it got so big that people
cómo se hizo una bola de que la gente
started saying that she was
empezó a decir que ella estaba hermano
sexist bro the blonde wasn't like that okay
machista el rubio no fue así vale
we hope the truth is he
esperamos la verdad
doesn't seem like a macho to me I refer to other
no me parece un machito remito a otras
women
mujeres
and
y
is the latest youtube food that's going to
es el último alimento de youtube que va
have 350 viewers
a tener 350 espectadores
that's how it's going to be  give
así le va a dar
I saw that in tweets it had like 600 700
yo vi que en tweet tenía como 600 700
other days and I saw it but
otros días y lo vi pero
criticism that are not criticisms they are
crítica que no son críticas son unos
cheap
baratos
liars
mentirosos
and so all the media turns it over
y así todos los medios lo voltean
we can see that we had an honor that has to be
podemos ver que teníamos un honor que
developed because of a
tenga que ser desarrollado porque
cancerous tumor they said it was a
tumoral cancerígena dijeron que era
lie and that I had cosmetic surgery
mentira y que yo me hice una operación
these tremendous ones this I just found out
estos tremendos esto me acabo de enterar
this is not seen that the truth you
esto no se ve que la verdad me lo habéis
told me now and it refers to this video
dicho ahora y se refiere a este vídeo
wind and deceived everyone everyone
wind y engañó a todos a todos tumor
false tumor and here is another video that you will
falso y aquí otro vídeo que luego lo
see later says the sauce of france do it again
veréis dice el salsa de france lo vuelva
puts in doubt the surgery of winding
a ser pone en duda la cirugía de winding
once again
una vez más
this false channel of frank shows that
este canal falso de frank demuestra que
its information content has no
su contenido de información no tiene
solid foundations since its
fundamentos sólidos ya que sus
arguments investigations are based on
argumentos investigaciones se basan en
rumors or positions and instead of
rumores o posiciones y en lugar de
going with respect with experts about what
acudir con especto con expertos sobre lo
winding lived, he relied on
que vivió winding se apoyó en
diagnoses of supposed
diagnósticos de supuestos estudiantes de
medical students he refers to this or in other words it was
medicina se refiere a esto o sea que fue
gold because when I heard this on
oro porque cuando yo escuché esto en
another day I said
otro día dije
who the [ __ ] doubted what
quién [__] puso en duda lo del tumor
winding's tumor and if in fact I remember well
de wind y si de hecho yo recuerdo bueno
I got along well with her at that time  I
yo me llevaba bien con ella en esa época
had a cordial relationship and I remember
tenía una relación cordial y yo recuerdo
doing a live show wishing her the
haber hecho un directo deseándole lo
best of course and I remember that the
mejor por supuesto y recuerdo que el
expert also I think in out he
perito también creo que en out el
also didn't
también no
freak out that things get ugly when we
flipando con que eso se pone feo cuando
go to iPhone raffles or
vamos sorteos de iphone o de 3000
$3,000 raffles he says that he put in that
dólares dice que metía que
seasonally and we have also looked for these $3,000
estacionalmente y estos 3.000 dólares
and I think he is
también lo hemos buscado y creo que se
referring to the turbo plan I don't think so I mean I
refiere al turbo plan no creo o sea yo
commented on the three thousand dollars that I am
comenté lo de los tres mil dólares que
giving away what I said was to put it as
sorteo lo que yo dije fue ponerlo de los
three thousand dollars and spread three thousand
tres mil dólares y regado tres mil
dollars among her followers
dólares entre sus seguidores
I never said that was false of
yo nunca dije que eso fuera falso por
course because I know very well that she
supuesto porque sé de sobra que ella
generates money to give away three thousand
genera dinero para regalar tres mil
dollars every week if she wants the thing is
dólares cada semana si quiere la cosa es
that what I did say was that
que lo que sí dije yo fue que
she did it in a way to look
ella lo hizo en cierto modo para quedar
good to wash herself a little because she
bien para lavarse un poquito porque lo
did it right when she was in the middle of
hizo justo cuando estaba en medio de
everything after the hurricane okay
todo de todo luego del huracán vale
when she gave me the extra and she gave him
cuando me puso a mí el extra y le puso
the extra of guarnizo water and she got into
el extra de agua guarnizo y se metió con
bg it's in a video so that's why
bg está en un vídeo entonces por eso
but she never went to 22 but I have
pero nunca ella fue a 22 pero sí que he
seen this video on turbo plan
visto este vídeo en turbo plan
in which she gave you  3000 dollars or
en el que te regalaba 3000 dólares o
something like that
algo así
then a few days ago by the
entonces yo hace unos días que por
way turbo plan 20 town day the
cierto turbo plan 20 día del pueblo el
debate
debate
from here in the youth asks you
desde aquí en la chavalería te lo pide
please come back from the town and make the
por favor vuelve ya del pueblo y hace el
debate point it's going to be two weeks or
punto debate van a ser ya dos semanas o
two and a half weeks
dos semanas y media
I was on vacation it's not Malaga
yo estaba de vacaciones no es málaga
when all the weight or not
cuando todo el peso o no
we are dragging this happens a
estamos arrastrando esto pasa hace una
week ago like this uploaded a video is that
semana así subió un vídeo es eso
talking about wind and that if
hablando de wind y que si no se quedó
the reviews didn't stay the typical and in this video
las reviews lo típico y en este vídeo
that I made a while ago we discussed the
que yo hice hace tiempo comentamos el
subject of the windy giveaway and me since I'm
tema del sorteo de windy y yo como soy
a big mouth I took it and said that most
un bocazas cogí y dije que muy
likely the windy giveaway was
probablemente el sorteo de windy era
fake like most giveaways
falso como la mayoría de sorteos que hay
on the internet well now wind too
en internet bueno que ahora también wind
and is doing fake giveaways well
y está haciendo sorteos falsos bueno
fake most likely all of this is
falsos muy seguramente todo esto sea
fake and wind took it and said so so well
falso y cogió wind y dijo así así pues
now I'm going to prove that the giveaway is
ahora voy a demostrar que el sorteo es
real to shut his mouth and that's what
verdadero para callarse la boca y eso ha
some of the Spanish critics have done they have
hecho algunos de los críticos españoles
said that my goals are fake
han dicho que mis metas falsas
since it ended it's so fake this
desde que acabara ya es tan falso esto
is serious
es grave
I ask for wind now on your channel a gift of three thousand
pido wind ya su canal regalo de tres mil
dollars and this happens by the way do you
dólares y pasa esto por cierto os
remember the time  this is the one that
acordáis de la época esta en la que todo
everyone put in the titles of the
el mundo ponía en los títulos de los
videos and this happens it was horrible it is not
vídeos y pasa esto era horrible no es
slander or union to defame in all of his
calumnia ni unión a difamar en todos sus
videos there is a false draw so that's
vídeos hay un sorteo falso entonces eso
the first thing wind and it is not slander and
lo primero wind y no es una calumnia y
defamation a crime for
una difamación un delito por de
information because we are not
información porque no te estamos
accusing you of any crime and apac
acusando de ningún delito y apac
the logic of turbo plan is that he is
la lógica de turbo plan es qué
telling her that he does false draws
le está diciendo que hace sorteos falsos
and says that he is not accusing her of any
y dice que no la está acusando de ningún
crime and then to turbo plan and he tells
delito y luego a turbo plan y le dice a
dallas that he could report him for
dallas que lo podría denunciar por
calling him a slanderer
llamarlo calumniador
turbo shut up now really
turbo cállate ya de verdad
false
falso
since be
ya que a [__]
careful with that then well the thing about the
cuidado con eso entonces bueno lo de los
draws here we have already located it I
sorteos aquí ya lo hemos localizado yo
think he is referring to turbo plan
creo que se refiere a turbo plan son
these are made
estos hechos
on youtube macho blondes when in my
en youtube machista rubios cuando en mi
direct video otherwise I prefer an
vídeo directo de lo contrario prefiera
environment many gays then will to
ambiente muchos gays entonces voluntad
see all my videos
de ver todo mis vídeos
in the videos of the parasites those of
en los vídeos de los parásitos esos de
criticisms that are not criticisms are
críticas que no son críticas son
lies and then they hate me because I know
mentiras y entonces me odian porque sé
that all the atrocities that they tell him
que todas las atrocidades que le dicen
feel
sentirse
and I am going to sue one and it will have
y voy a demandar a uno y le va a tener
all the juice and it will have  that pay me
todo el jugo y va a tener que pagarme
money
dinero
the mother that I already have all the evidence
la madre que ya tengo toda la evidencia
even if she modifies her videos go to
aunque modifique sus vídeos se vaya a la
hell to the same
[__] a la misma [__] se vaya
[ __ ] go we see her very sure we see her very sure that she is going to send someone to hell of course here the first doubt that I would have would be who will be the controversial youtube who is going to denounce okay controversial youtuber that there is in dealing with
youtuber de polémica que haya en tratar
the subject of winding javi oliveira turbo
el tema de winding javi oliveira turbo
plan wilhite the great forward
plan wilhite el gran delantero
fran
el socio de fran
spirit's partner atv the
spirit atv
love one is only a video 2 but
la de amor es solamente un vídeo 2 pero
well the counter sack
bueno el saco counter
the sun
el sol
let's say that these ten would be the
digamos que estos diez serían los
main ones no
principales no
these 10 would be the main ones in
estos 10 serían los principales en
number of videos in number of videos the
número de vídeos en número de vídeos la
truth is that
verdad
of all of them all of them all
que de todos todos
we are going to see those of turbo plan
vamos a ver los de turbo plan
the name of videos has nothing to
el nombre de videos no tiene nada que
do with this I want to make it very clear before
ver esto quiero dejarlo muy claro antes
checking it the number of videos does not
de comprobarlo el número de vídeos no
matter because it does not matter if it is tura a
importa porque da igual sea si tura un
controversial channel they deal with current events
canal de polémicas tratan la actualidad
I can take a week or two
yo puedo llevarme una semana o dos
weeks uploading videos
semanas subiendo todos los días vídeos
about the same youtuber every day while
sobre el mismo youtuber mientras que es
on youtube this one that week
en youtube este esa semana en la
currently is what there is you understand the
actualidad es lo que hay me entiende el
number of  videos it doesn't matter maybe
número de vídeos no importa a lo mejor
on youtubers v300 videos about the same
en youtubers v300 vídeos sobre la misma
person and he doesn't commit any crime and maybe
persona y no comete ningún delito y a lo
after u2 see he uploads two videos about
mejor tras u2 ver sube dos vídeos sobre
the same person and in these two videos he
la misma persona y en estos dos vídeos
commits a crime some information
comete un delito alguna información
some slander or some [ __ ]
alguna calumnia o al cualquier [__]
okay then he but let's see next it
vale entonces él pero a ver siguiente
touches a little in the nose not the number
toca un poco en las narices no el número
of videos then the turbo plan I would
de vídeos entonces el turbo plan yo
say that it is tremendous the hard plan I would
diría que es tremendo lo duro plan yo
say infinite videos us an
diría que infinitos vídeos nosotros un
infinite plan let's say no
plan infinito digamos no
and even videos that are not for her the
e incluso vídeos que no son para ella la
new wind and wind and she has attacked me by
nueva wind y wind y me ha atacado por
birds and berga and in the cleavage
aves y berga y en el escote
if your plan is infinite
si es que tú lo plan es infinito
wind and steam maria
wind y vapor maría
windows windows turned
windows windows vuelto
right wing
wing derecho
wind and I would put please
wind y metería por favor
my mother windy
madre mía windy
uy diaz the ridiculous in red very diet it
uy díaz el ridículo en tinto muy dieta
's not right I bought the melide
no está bien compre el pad de melide
wind pad and I is that it is infinite it
wind y yo es que es infinito
is infinite
es infinito
and that you can be downloading 8000 days
y que puedes estar bajando 8000 días
how many videos can be
cuántos vídeos pueden ser
very indie against me al khalifa how many
muy indie contra mí al khalifa cuantos
videos could someone be could count
vídeos podrían ser alguien podría contar
the ones I already say is that as if you make
los que ya digo es que como si tú haces
300 videos of the  same person I
300 vídeos de la misma persona yo
surely with all the extracts that I
seguramente con todos los extractos que
do in my live from Dallas I have made
hago en mi directo de dallas haya hecho
500 because because if every day there are
500 porque porque si todos los días hay
politicians with Dallas then every
políticos con dallas pues yo todos los
day I talk about Dallas I understand
días hablo de dallas me entiende
the time of Dallas with which I will make many
la época de dallas con la me haré muchos
videos of Mieres the number does not matter what
vídeo de mieres no importa el número lo
matters is the content what is
que importa es el contenido lo que se
said inside okay let's see let's
diga dentro vale vamos a ver
see I have made many videos about
a ver yo he hecho muchos vídeos sobre
Windy and what I have done yes they have been
windy y lo que he hecho sí que han sido
more defending her than anything else okay
más defendiéndola que otra cosa vale
but well
pero bueno
in some she criticizes her of course
en algunos le critica por supuesto
when it seemed appropriate to me but
cuando me ha parecido conveniente pero
my video The Wind and how many could I have
yo vídeo the wind y cuantos podría haber
made
hecho
can you see
podrá ver
or mean there could be 10 maybe
o sea podrá haber 10 a lo mejor
10 videos 89 we are
10 videos 89
not going to see you in Out Now you have the same
no te vamos a ver en out now ten igual
as me
que yo
an author the same as me
un autor igual que yo
although not
aunque tampoco
good a little more a little more
bueno un poco más un poco más
but not much
pero tampoco mucho
the other side has three or four more than
la otra lado tiene tres o cuatro más que
them who do I
ellos
tell you to look
quien os digo a buscar
for a certain channel and congratulations on your
por cierto canal y felicidades por tu
million from here put it on my behalf
millón desde aquí ponérselo de mi parte
everyone on twitter the kids
todo el mundo en twitter la chavalería
congratulate you on the million
te felicita por el millón
oh I
uy
don't know how when you have a million
no sé cómo cuando tienes un millón de
subscribers you also get it  I say let's see
suscriptores también te lo digo a ver
cry crazy it sounds to me like he's made
cry crazy me suena a mí que haya hecho
quite a few videos
bastante vídeos
crazy may have his
crazy puede tener sus
not that much do
tampoco tanto
you think he could have about 20 or 30 videos
creeis podrá tener unos 20 o 30 vídeos
let's see about wind and no more and I'm following
vemos sobre wind y no más y me siguiendo
very high the thing doesn't matter the
muy arriba la cosa no importa la
amount of video doesn't matter but of
cantidad de vídeo no importa pero yo de
all the youtuber of criticism I would
todos los youtuber de críticas yo
close the net on the possibilities
cerraría el cerco a las posibilidades
okay
vale
to javi oliveira and turbo plan
a javi oliveira y turbo plan
because they are the two that have the
porque son de los dos que tienen los
data and to whom the
datos y a los que nos ha mandado la
certified letter with the presence has not
carta certificada con la presencia no
and when I received the letter
han y cuando me llegó la carta
honestly it didn't even make me nervous
sinceramente es que ni me puso nervioso
and I was calm because
y yo estaba tranquilo por el hecho de
I know I already have my ass bald with
que yo sé ya tengo el culo pelado con
this lawsuits and let's always have
esto de las demandas y haber siempre
any of the
pueden denunciar cualquiera de los
youtubers that I mentioned in any
youtubers que yo mencioné en cualquier
of my video put can report not clarify why to the
de mi vídeo poner no aclare no porque al
channel to send any letter or here
canal a mandar ninguna carta ni acá
then if here I would send a letter I would
entonces si acá la mandaría una carta yo
close the net on javi oliveira in
cerraría el cerco en javi oliveira en
turbo plan to one of those two okay
turbo plan a uno de esos dos vale
I have it will happen very skin with the
yo tengo ocurrirá muy pela con las
complaints and the two I say any
denuncias y los dos digo cualquier
person who appears in my video can
persona que sale en mi vídeo me puede
report me how can you report yourself
denunciar como poder te puedes denunciar
now that  I won something else you have to keep in
ahora que gane ya otra cosa hay que
mind one thing and that when you
tener en cuenta una cosa y que cuando tú
file a civil lawsuit
pones una demanda por lo civil siempre
you always risk that if you lose it you have to
te arriesgas a que si la pierdes tienes
pay you have to pay the
que pagar tienes que pagarle tú las
things to the person you are suing
cosas a la persona a la que denuncia
okay if someone sues me for a
vale si alguien a mí me denuncia por lo
civil lawsuit and loses they have to pay me a
civil y pierde me tiene que pagar un
good percentage of what they were
buen porcentaje de lo que me estaba
asking me then you have to go to apart
pidiendo entonces tienes que ir a parte
from the lawyer's fees you have to
de los gastos de abogado ya tienes que
be very very very very sure to
estar muy muy muy muy seguro para
sue someone okay when she
denunciar a alguien vale yo cuando me
sent me some easy we just reviewed
mandó algunos fácil solamente revisamos
the videos it's that there was nothing illegal
los vídeos es que no había nada ilegal
in fact in most of my
es que de hecho en la mayoría de mis
videos I treated her
vídeos la trataba
better or rather more in favor than against I
mejor o sea más a favor que en contra la
have defended her more than anything else yes it's
he defendido más que otra cosa sí que
true that it stung me I feel very
verdad que me pique me siento como muy
bad when she put the extra it's because
mal cuando me puso el extra es porque
obviously and there maybe she can say
obvio y ahí a lo mejor puede decirle
something to her like I don't think she's a good person or
algo como no me parece buena persona o
something like that more you know but nothing that
alguna cosa así más sabes pero nada que
could have the magnitude to
pueda tener la envergadura como para
report you know and she asked me to
denunciar lo sabes y ella me pedía que
remove the videos
retirarse los vídeos
in that certificate her lawyer asked me to
en ese certificado su abogado me pedía
remove the videos and also
que retirarse los vídeos y que además
because at a given moment we are going to
porque en un momento dado lo vamos a
remove some video I don't usually do that
retirar algún vídeo no lo suelo hacer
with anyone okay  but before going to
con nadie vale pero antes que llegar a
trial and wasting time and money on a
un juicio y perder el tiempo y dinero un
lawyer all that, well look if they
abogado todo eso pues mira si te
need a video that I already
necesitan algún vídeo que ya el vídeo ya
knew nothing about the video then he removed it
lo sabido nada de nada pues lo quitó
but he also asked me to
pero es que además me pedía pedirle
apologize to him and it's like how am I going to do and
disculpas y es como como voy a hacer y
a video asking for forgiveness if he doesn't disrespect you
un vídeo pidiendo disculpas si no te
ever, I mean that the
falta el respeto nunca osea que gaste el
other day I spent the joke about all of Morocco on
otro día la broma de todo marruecos de
your channel with the chat bag it's
tu canal con la bolsa del chat
not that I don't think he's a good person
no es que no me parece buena persona
because he put the extra on his
porque me ha puesto el extra en su
hanger I
percha
don't consider it that I thanks to the bible
no lo considero que yo gracias la biblia
without wind and turbo I wouldn't have arrived in
sin wind y turbo no hubiera llegado en
sugar no now
azúcar no ahora
I also reached a million and you didn't
yo también llegué al millón y no me
greet me well congratulations and I'm a member I didn't
saludaste pues felicidades y soy miembro
know I didn't know you cool
no lo sabía no te conocía chula
congratulations on the million the bible hey well
felicidades por el millón la biblia oye
in a month promo well it proved to me that I've been
pues al mes promo pues me probó que yo
here for a month we did between the
llevo un mes están acá hicimos entre la
fight for the injured out in roll and the
pelea por el out herido en rollo la y la
host that takes me here and there I've been
[__] que me lleva por aquí por allá
here for a month and if you see me that I
llevo un mes están acá y si me ves que
only earn a thousand the thing that I didn't
solamente gana mil la cosa que yo no
consider is that it's not that I didn't
consideraban es que no es que no
consider that there was nothing there was no
consideraba que no había nada no había
information nothing that  I would get out of
ninguna información nada que saliera de
freedom of expression there was nothing
la libertad de expresión no había nada
like I'm going to apologize for that
como te voy a pedir disculpa por eso
of course always before going
yo por supuesto siempre antes de llegar
to court
a un juzgado juzgado
I prefer to be on good terms with people and
prefiero quedar de buena con la gente y
fix things but the thing is that there is nothing so
arreglar pero es que no hay nada por lo
I was not going to make a video
que yo no iba a ser un vídeo pidiendo
apologizing because I do not
disculpas porque yo no le falta el
disrespect her or rather I'm going to make a video
respeto o sea que voy a hacer un vídeo
saying I'm so sorry wind and you
diciendo lo siento mucho wind y tú
're right ari had no execution the
tienes la razón ari no tuvo ejecución el
video the wind and been to
vídeo the wind y estado en sesiones de
conar sessions and he did not accuse her of anything directly
conar y no la acusó de nada directamente
although he suspects he did not insult her he did not
aunque sospeche no la insultó no le
disrespect her what I'm saying that I
faltó el respeto que estoy diciendo que
think she was obsessed with someone I
creo que estaba obsesionada con alguien
believe it is that it is that it is that you are
que lo creo es que es que es que estás
waiting to see if eric does the he
pendiente de si eric hace la le pide
apologizes to kimberley you put a tweet if
disculpas a kimberley pones un tweet si
I will do it he apologized to dallas you put
haré le pidió disculpas a dallas pones
a tweet share it is the thread the video of
un tweet comparte es el hilo el vídeo
mine was completely denying and
ese mío era desmintiendo completamente y
giving context to each publication the
dándole contexto a cada publicación el
pose is worth it
pose se vale
total that and apart from that I think that I
total que y aparte a mí yo creo que yo
think that in reality
creo que en realidad
the feeling that I get at
yo la sensación que a mí me da de
first is that the certified letter was
primera es que la carta certificada iba
only going to be for turbo plan from the
solamente para turbo plan desde el
first moment because  there was a person
primer momento porque había una persona
who was mediating between that lawyer
que estaba mediando entre ese abogado
who was known from another youtube and windi
que era conocido de otro youtube y windi
so that he would send him the turbo plan letter
para que le mandase la carta turbo plan
okay and that already on the way like a thousand I
vale y que ya de camino como a mil yo
had he agreed with me in the video that
tuve me dio la razón en el vídeo que
wind and put in and to wind and that video
wind y metido y a wind y ese vídeo le
bothered him a lot because I agreed with
molestaba mucho porque yo le daba la
juan well I think they put me in too and
razón a juan pues creo que también me
javi is going to send me a letter
metieron y me va a mandar una carta javi
too to see if I can get javi to remove it
también a ver si consigo que javi lo
but it's that a video of me
pero es que sería ridículo un vídeo mío
apologizing for something would be ridiculous because there is
pidiéndole disculpas por algo porque es
nothing is what I have
que no hay nada es lo que yo le haya
disrespected the opponent
falta de respeto al contrario
as long as there was no injustice
siempre que no había una injusticia
towards wind and I'm going to continue saying it
hacia wind y lo voy a seguir diciendo
anyway even though it seems to me that what he
igualmente aunque me parezca que muy mal
did to me by giving me the strike was very bad and that it did
lo que me hizo de ponerme el strike y
n't seem to me that he was a good
que no me pareció ahí que fuese buena
person when he put us there, it's okay with me but
persona al ponernos está ya me vale pero
that doesn't take away my objectivity or for
eso no quita mi objetividad o por
example he still criticizes forward with
ejemplo todavía critica delantero con
that video okay
ese vídeo vale
now well now well now well
ahora bien
now well
ahora bien ahora bien ahora bien
anyway I offered him javi try to
igualmente yo le ofrecí javi trata de
talk to wind and like adults
hablar con wind y como personas adultas
and ask them what bothers them in
y pregúntales que lo que le molesta en
the most mature way
lo más maduro
well I am available to talk more
pues estoy disponible para hablar más
removed the block of  twitter but I
quitado el bloqueo de twitter pero yo
can talk about it but let's see
puedo hablarlo pero es que a ver
sincerely they are videos that are not my
sinceramente son vídeos que no son mi
opinion and I did not know if they would remove and
opinión y es que no sabía quitaran y
apologize for my opinion okay I can
disculpar por mi opinión vale puedo
talk to her and I can be at peace with
hablar con ella y puedo estar en paz con
her and cordially but I am not going to remove
ella y cordialmente pero no voy a quitar
any video because she disrespected me
ningún vídeo porque me le faltó al
and in my opinion and also it
respeto y en mi opinión y además me
bothered me a lot that they put it
molestó muchísimo que me metieron está
there and I am not going to give her the reason to
ahí y no le voy a dar la razón a que le
put it there would be one either and the
pongan estarían one tampoco y el propio
dalai himself the one who uploaded also says the same
dalai el subido también dice lo mismo
okay
vale
equally my lawyer offered her because
igualmente mi abogada le ofreció porque
in the command letter she told me very
ella en la carta de mando me ponía muy
few things to the coma turbo plan to
pocas cosas a los coma turbo plan que le
put a list of things not to me in the
poner una lista de cosas no a mí en la
letter she told me that she had received
carta me ponía que ella había recibido
threats or insults for my videos and
amenazas o insultos por mis vídeos y
then I told her my lawyer I say
entonces le dije mi abogada le digo
okay then send us those insults so
bueno pues mándanos esos insultos que
we can see them send us all those
nosotros los veamos mandarnos todas esas
screenshots and javi agrees in a
capturas y javi se compromete en un
live to make a video
directo a hacer un vídeo
waiting for him a slap on the wrist to all
esperándolo un tirón de orejas a todos
the followers who get into this type of
los seguidores que cojan en este tipo de
things that I have already done that to I mean
cosas que eso ya lo he hecho yo a o sea
in fact I have a video on my main channel I have
de hecho tengo en mi canal principal un
on my channel  a video
vídeo tengo en mi canal un vídeo
dedicated to criticizing people who
dedicado a criticar a la gente que se
get into the comments with wind and
mete en los comentarios con wind y
then I can't offer you
y entonces yo ahí no puedo ofrecerle
anything and the turbo plan the letter was the
nada y el turbo plan la carta fue la
same except that in the turbo plan it
misma solamente que en la de turbo plan
was included with something else that mine didn't and that
iba incluida a otra cosa que la mía no y
is that to turbo it said we consider that
es que a turbo le ponía consideramos que
you have expressions in your videos that are not
tienes en tus vídeos expresiones que no
protected under freedom of expression that does
se amparan bajo la libertad de expresión
n't say it in my letter it
eso a mí no me lo pone en la carta a mí
said to me that because of me there were
me ponía que por mi culpa había
hateful comments whether she does or not that's
comentarios de odio sea ella o no así
okay but it didn't say the
vale pero a mí no me ponía lo de la
freedom of pressure thing to me because
libertad de presión porque es que
obviously my expressions are within
evidentemente mis expresiones van dentro
freedom a member here
de la libertad un miembro aquí
tell me your name when you let me know that you
decirme el nombre cuando me avise que
're recording and I can't see it
estoy grabando y no lo veo
your children and your heart thank you very much
sus hijos y el corazón muchísimas
welcome
gracias bienvenida
basically my expressions in work
básicamente mis expresiones en trabajan
within freedom of expression and to
dentro de la libertad expresión y a
turbo plan it said we consider that your
turbo plan le ponía consideramos que tus
expressions are not within freedom of
expresiones no están en la libertad
expression and make it a turbo plan I
expresión y hazla de turbo plan le
added something else which was the issue of those
añadía otra cosa que era el tema de los
of the live to that turbo plan has made
de los live a que turbo plan ha hecho
videos reacting to the live and in
vídeos reaccionando a los live and en
the live a it is private content that
los live a es un contenido privado que
is paid and you have to pay to see that
es de pago y hay que pagar para verlo
no  you can publish it in a video, I
eso no lo puedes publicar en un vídeo yo
did it with the one from 20 the end
lo hice con el de 20 el fin
obviously sells the end is not going to
obviamente vende el fin no se va a poner
report anyone because the
a denunciar de nadie porque el pack de
best of the end pack is already more than filtered and
best del fin está ya más que filtrar y
ximo everywhere or the photo of
ximo por todos lados o sea la foto de
live at the bell dolphins also
live at the bell delfines también
twitter to be but turbo the that does not
twitter estar pero turbo los eso no da
matter
igual
I am not a lawyer or jurist and I can be
no soy abogado ni jurista y me puedo
wrong but I think that you can not
equivocar pero yo creo que no se puede
teach although it is known in the south in with the calm
enseñar aunque se en sur en con la calma
of Dallas the intimate part is worth because you
de dallas la parte íntima vale porque
are giving you are teaching the content
estás dando estás enseñando el contenido
that is inside it is as if I take and
que hay dentro es como si yo cojo y
put here now in the disciples and I
pongo aquí ahora en el discípulas y
put here the live the movie and
pongo aquí el directo la película y
some angular reaction and I only know the
alguna reacción angular y se sólo las
faces of the characters
caras de los personajes
I think that can not be done in
yo creo que eso no se puede hacer de
fact when you register in the ifa
hecho cuando te registras en el ifa
when you register for a live the
cuando te registras en un live a lo
first thing it tells you is that you keep in
primero que te pone es que tengas en
mind that people cannot
cuenta que la gente no se puede
download your content in fact it does not give you
descargar tu contenido de hecho no te da
the option to download the photos
la opción para descargar las fotos
you have to take a screenshot
tienes que hacer una captura de pantalla
or something like that you have to make a
o algo así tienes que hacer una
strategy and it warns you that it is
estrategia y te avisa de que es
completely illegal and that you can
completamente ilegal y que puedes
report whoever  publish or spread your
denunciar a quien publique o difunda tus
photos from there it does not pass of course people do
fotos de ahí no pasa de claro la gente
not have money to report okay
no tiene dinero para denunciar vale
but the content of lifan can not be
pero el contenido de lifan no se puede
shown okay I think okay
enseñar vale yo creo vale
I have made the dolphin video I uploaded it a
yo he hecho el vídeo del delfín lo subí
few hours later I removed it because I said this
a la poca hora lo quite porque dije esto
apart from that it does not lead me to monetize
aparte que no me lleva a monetizar
digester it is not good it is not good no matter how
digestor no está bien no está bien por
much you censor the passage I saw many
mucho que censure el pasaje vi muchos
videos there it is from Craig there were
vídeos por ahí es de craig había por
about five or six videos already watching the
unos cinco o seis vídeos ya viendo los
live and them the dolphin and now nothing more
live and them el delfín y ya nada más
than more that I have seen but green feint
que más que he visto pero verde finta se
starts to report but if you are a youtube
pone a denunciar pero si eres un youtube
that already wind and has between be and be
que ya wind y tiene entre sea y sea
because it has already made like 400 500
porque ya lo ha hecho como 400 500
videos the same since you have done it you
vídeos los mismos ya que hagas hecho
know then that is what I added to
sabes entonces eso es lo que le añadí a
the certified letter that is what I
la carta certificada eso es lo que le
added in addition to the turbo plan that is why I
añadí además al turbo plan por eso yo
say that
digo que
when whiskey says I am going to screw him I am going
cuando whisky dice lo voy a [__] lo voy
to send him to hell if it were me if it were
a mandar a la [__] si fuera yo si
me if it was the same it is me someone is going to
fuera yo si lo mismo soy yo alguien va a
report she has said that she is going to
denunciar ella ha dicho que va a
report one I would close the fence
denunciar a uno yo el cerco lo cerraría
between turbo  plan and I because they are the
entre turbo plan y yo porque son a los
two of those who have the data to whom
dos de los que tienen los datos a los
the letter is sent if it were me and
que nos manda la carta si fuera a mí y
suddenly it were a complaint for the
de repente fuera una denuncia por
right to honor
derecho al honor
by civil because by criminal and by
por lo civil porque por lo penal y por
criminal impossible by criminal
lo penal imposible por lo penal
impossible because by criminal it has to
imposible porque por lo penal tiene que
be that someone accuses you of a crime and
ser que alguien te acuse de un delito y
all the slander okay but
todas las una calumnia vale pero
let's imagine that it was by civil okay to screw
imaginemos que fuera por lo civil vale a
me I wouldn't screw myself Mariah
mí joderme no me jodería mariah
bend over money for a lawyer to defend myself and
agacharme dinero en abogado defenderme y
if she if she loses which would be the most
si ella si ella pierde que sería lo más
likely because there is nothing in my
probable porque no hay nada en mis
videos that has damaged her honor and her
vídeos que haya dañado su honor y su
dignity she would have to pay the
dignidad me tendría que pagar ella las
costs
costas
and the thing is that losing a complaint losing a
y es que perder una denuncia perder una
complaint
denuncia
if you file a complaint you lose it you are going to
si tú pone una denuncia la pierde vas a
look worse because you are going to give rise to
quedar peor porque vas a dar pie a que
other people you know
otra gente sabe
but thank you Daniel welcome to
pero es que gracias daniel bienvenido a
a very strong hug
un abrazo muy fuerte
but I if I were to report only
pero yo yo si fuese a denunciar solo a
one and Díaz for someone who would be more
uno y díaz por alguien que fuera más
likely I don't know who you think
seguro no sé a quién creéis ustedes que
can report
puede denunciar
who you think will be the injured one
a quien creen ustedes que será el herido
and the other I say imaginary that for whatever reason it
y el otro digo imaginarios que por lo
was me and I have the bad
que sea fuese a mí y yo tengo la mala
luck that the  I lose because the judge
suerte de que la pierdo porque el juez
interprets that one of my comments
interpreta que uno de mis comentarios
could damage her image, she would
pueden dañar su imagen
put a cover page on me that five thousand
me pondría una portada de que cinco mil
ten thousand or in other words, screw me, sink me, she names me,
diez mil o sea joderme hundir me nombra
sink me in [ __ ],
hundir en la [__]
however, if it were another person
sin embargo si ya fuese a otra persona a
who she could report for showing
quien la pueda denunciar por mostrar
private content, for slander, for
contenido privado por calumnias por
many things, for ideas, and we will be
muchas cosas a ideas y estaremos
talking about many things that would add up to
hablando de muchas cosas que sumarían
something bigger, do you
algo más grande
understand me? And here she has referred to
me entendéis y aquí se te ha referido a
someone that she is sure that she is going to
alguien que ella está seguro que lo va a
screw her
[__]
and also says no matter how much she modifies
y además dice por mucho que modifique
your videos or no matter how much she edited her
tus vídeos o por mucho que editó sus
videos, she
vídeos
could be referring to the fact that she disturbed the
se puede referir a que turbó los vídeos
live videos and censored them, we
de los live and los censura
will go to Vargas to José Ángel Romano
iremos en vargas a josé ángel romano
and
y
[Music]
[Música]
who is now talking about the issue of the
que ahora vuelve a hablar del tema de la
complaint again
denuncia
[Music] they
[Música]
put the toxic Bertos shampoo on him, for
le ponen el champú bertos tóxico por
this I suspect that it could be me
esto yo sospecho que podría ser yo
too because when they tell her power, cough
también porque cuando le dicen poder tos
and sex,
y sexo
what they do in their videos to speak ill
lo que hacen sus vídeos para hablar mal
of me and defame me and put your parents on me
de mí y difamarme y ponerme tus padres
who is not talking about a general cough and
que no está hablando general de tos y
adult turbo iron, media that
adulta turbo plancha medios que hacen
line up to make me look bad because  you guys
filas para hacerme de mal porque ustedes
tell stories about meals to make someone have a bad
cuento de comidas para hacer tener mal
wind and I don't think it's like that, each of us
wind y yo creo que no sea así cada uno
makes our own videos on our own,
hacemos nuestros vídeos por nuestra
in fact, getting together a group to disarm
cuenta
someone sounds more like
a alguien a mí me suena más a lo del
this twitter thread to me, not his thread, and the
hilo este de twitter no el hilo él y lo
opposite. Yes, I see it more like getting together
contrario eso sí lo veo más como juntar
as groups and to leave malaria
como conjuntas y para dejar malaria
because someone made the thread and there were
porque alguien hizo el hilo y ahí hubo
several people who helped
varias personas que ayudaron a
collect evidence and you are in charge of
recopilada prueba y tú te encargas de
spreading it,
darle difusión
the vector game is very overwhelming, Mr. Palencia, it does
la partida de vectores señor palencia
n't stop there, say something
ahí no para vuelve a decir alguna cosa
new
nueva
to the water cattle again, I'm
al ganado
going to start with a pause because it's been full
voy a empezar con pausa que ha sido full
full there,
full hay
but where does Vice want to go,
pero a dónde quiere llegar a vice ya
we already know that he's going to denounce the turbo
sabemos que va a denunciar el turbo al
plan
plan
then I'm simply recording the
luego simplemente estoy grabando el
checklist America through a secondary channel, I would
check list américa por canal secundario
n't have any part and no,
no tendría ninguna parte y no
just bet that people leave me out of the
simplemente apuesta que me dejen de los
comments, who thinks they'll be
comentarios la gente quien cree que será
the lucky one? I
el afortunado
already said the fence I would close between
yo el cerco ya lo digo lo cerraría entre
Xavi Oliveira and Turbo Plan, but if I
xavi oliveira y turbo plan pero si lo
say it better, maybe it's both,
digo mejor a lo mejor es a los dos
but she who speaks in the singular
pero que ella que habla en singular
when she says she's going to denounce one,
cuando dice que va a denunciar a uno
look
mira
when we get to the end, the game to
cuando lleguemos a terminar partida para
jump, copy from Guajira
saltar copy de guajira
[Music]
[Música]
you deserve it open
su mereces abierta
well basically
bueno básicamente
[Music]
[Música]
also your own features and not your own
también tus propios rasgos y no propios
basically there was one more moment there was
básicamente había un momento más
another moment in front that
había otro momento delante que
basically what I was saying was I have to
básicamente lo que venía diciendo era
do it I have to report
tengo que hacerlo tengo que denunciar a
this person because when I report
esta persona porque cuando yo denuncia a
someone and they pay me the others are going to
uno y me pague ya los demás van a
think twice when it comes to lying
pensárselo dos veces a la hora de mentir
about me it
sobre mí
leaves us after after the set but I
nos deja después tras la puesta pero me
found it curious man shout what's up and
pareció curioso hombre grito que tal y
thom good night I found it
thom buena noche me pareció curioso que
curious that this live was taken only the clip of the forward was cut Vidal had been made and the importance was not given to these others he tells me that for me it is very relevant because we would be talking we will be talking about a new arc in the anime of the complaints and in this
en el anime de las denuncias y en este
case we will have Wind as the protagonist
caso tendremos como protagonista a wind
and against an enemy that would be a
y contra un enemigo que sería un canal
criticism channel or rather you know the range
de críticas o sea ya sabéis el abanico
of criticism channels which one
de canales de críticas cuál
and leave me in the comment box
y dejarme en la caja de comentarios
who do you think will be the chosen one who do
quién creéis ustedes que será el elegido
you think would be the chosen one
quién cree usted que sería el elegido
okay I'll tell you if it were to go to Webber I
vale ya os digo yo si fuera a webber yo
in fact when I denounce someone there
de hecho cuando denunció a alguien
are lawyers who ask for all the
hay abogados que te piden todas las
complaints okay there are lawyers that you
denuncias vale hay abogados que tú le
go to as they are going to charge yes or yes whether you
llegas como ellos van a cobrar sí o sí
lose or win they ask for all the
pierdas o ganes te piden todas las
complaints and there is one thing to keep in
denuncias y hay una cosa a tener en
mind that the complaint when you
cuenta que la denuncia cuando las
lose them when you file them and you do not win you
pierdes cuando las pones y no las gana
lose the money and not only do you
pierdes el dinero y no solamente que
lose the money but when it is through
pierda el dinero sino que cuando es por
civil proceedings you have to pay the other person who
la vía civil tiene que pagarle al otro
has reported you have to pay them
al que ha denunciado tienes que pagarle
things okay
las cosas vale
imagine reporting someone imagine a
imagínate denuncia a alguien imaginaros
vegetable complaint or vegetable complaint and
denuncia vegetal o denuncia vegetal y
now I lose and I have to pay them the
ahora pierdo y le tengo que pagar la
old age is what
vejez está lo que se le gastaban
lawyers spent on me in judicial processes on a
abogados yo en procesos judiciales en un
lawyer in a process for example
abogado en un en un proceso por ejemplo
I spent eight thousand euros well
me gasté ocho mil euros
that you have to pay seven datatur
pues eso tienes que pagar siete datatur
money on lawyers what he has for the
dinero en abogados lo que tiene para el
floor also if he loses be to
suelo también si pierde sea para
report who it is that I was very sure
denunciar quién es que estaba muy seguro
and the lawyers who have class and
y los abogados que tienen clase y
professionalism warn you because I my
profesionalidad te avisa porque yo mi
lawyer the one who will lose it I
abogado el que él mismo perderá la
read a lot of times with things that have
leído un montón de veces con cosas que
happened to me and what I want to report
me han pasado y lo que quiero denunciar
this stability is this
esta estabilidad es este
saying this has no pressure outside this did
dicho esto no tiene presión fuera esto
not go were you know case that they are going to
no fuera fueron sabes caso que vayan a
win only
ganar solamente